marketingwithanik.com 2019-06-29

# Lurn - A Transformational Home for Entrepreneurs!

## Lurn.com Privacy Policy

## Updated May 23, 2018

* * *

This Privacy Policy applies to your use of www.lurn.com (the "Site") owned by Lurn, Inc. its subsidiaries, affiliates and partners (collectively "Lurn"). Your privacy is very important to us. We want to make your experience on our Site as enjoyable and rewarding as possible, and we want you to use the information, tools, and opportunities we provide through our Site with complete confidence.

We have created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy and security. This Privacy Policy describes how our company collects information from all end users of the services we provide on or through the Site (the "Services") - those who access some of our Services but do not have accounts ("Visitors") as well as those who may purchase products and/or pay a monthly service fee to subscribe to the Service ("Members") - what we do with the information we collect, and the choices Visitors and Members have concerning the collection and use of such information. We request that you read this Privacy Policy carefully.

For purposes of the EU General Data Protection Regulation (the "GDPR") the data controller is Lurn, Inc., **2098 Gaither Rd, Rockville, MD 20850**

If you have questions or complaints regarding our Privacy Policy or practices, please contact us at [privacy@lurn.com](mailto:privacy@lurn.com).

### Lurn's Privacy Principles

Lurn follows the following principles in order to protect your privacy:

  * We do not collect any more personally identifiable information about you than is necessary;
  * We only use your personally identifiable information for the purposes we specify in this Privacy Policy, unless you agree otherwise;
  * We do not keep your personally identifiable information if it is no longer needed; and
  * Other than as we specify in this Privacy Policy, we do not share your personally identifiable information with third parties.

### Information We Collect

We collect personally identifiable information from you if you request information from us, sign up to join our email lists, register for an account, participate in our promotions, such as contests and sweepstakes, take our surveys, use or purchase our Products and Services, contact us about a purchase, or email, call or otherwise communicate with us.

In order for you to initiate or complete a purchase from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form, including your contact information (such as name, email or shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date).

If you purchase a product or service for someone else, we will also collect the name and address of that person so that we can process your order and ship the products, as applicable. When you provide us with this information we will only use it for the specific reason for which it is collected.

When Visitors or Members download, install and use Lurn Services on their mobile phone or other wireless telecommunications device, Lurn automatically gathers information, including without limitation, carrier providers, unique device identifiers, geo-location information (if allowed by the user), the types of mobile devices accessing the services, and the types of operating systems accessing the services (collectively, "Mobile Device Data"). A unique device identifier is a string of alphanumeric characters (similar to a serial number) used to uniquely identify and distinguish each mobile phone or other wireless communications device. Location services can be enabled or disabled at any time, through the settings on your mobile device. Lurn uses Mobile Device Data to understand usage patterns and to improve our Products, Services and functionality of our Site.

Lurn automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, domain type, browser version, service provider, cookies, and the pages you request. This data is used in the aggregate. We link this automatically collected data to personally identifiable information.

### How We Use Your Information

Information we collect may be used in the following ways:

  * To notify you of updates to our Site or any Products or Services we offer.
  * To respond to your requests or inquiries.
  * To process and complete your transactions, including, as applicable, customer service, order confirmation, billing, delivering Products or Services, and otherwise fulfill our contractual obligations to you.
  * To provide you with newsletters, articles, or programs, Products, or Services, alerts and announcements.
  * To share offers from other companies with you.
  * To conduct market research.
  * To analyze transactions and purchase histories to improve our products, services, programs and other offerings.
  * As necessary to verify and validate your identity.
  * To keep records of our interactions with you if you place an order or otherwise deal with our representatives.
  * To prevent, investigate or provide notice of fraud, unlawful or criminal activity, or unauthorized access to or use of personally identifiable information, our Site or data systems.
  * To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights.
  * To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide your personally identifiable information to us.

### Your Rights

You have the right to request a copy of any personally identifiable information that we hold about you. If you would like a copy of your personally identifiable information, please contact us using the contact information below. We may request proof of your identity before sharing such information. If you discover that the information we hold about you is incorrect or out of date, you may ask us to correct that information by emailing us at [privacy@lurn.com](mailto:privacy@lurn.com).

You may ask us to delete the personally identifiable data we hold about you in certain circumstances. It may not be possible for us to delete all of the information we hold about you where we are fulfilling a transaction or have a legal basis to retain the information, however please contact us to discuss how we can assist you with your request.

When we process your information on the basis that you have consented to such processing, you have the right to withdraw your consent, or ask us to stop or restrict processing the personally identifiable information we have about you, at any time by emailing us at [privacy@lurn.com](mailto:privacy@lurn.com).

You may also ask us to transfer your personally identifiable information to a third party in certain circumstances. If you would like any further information about your rights or how to exercise them, please contact us.

Please direct any questions, including any requests to exercise your legal rights, to [privacy@lurn.com](mailto:privacy@lurn.com).

If you are in the European Union, you have the right to make a complaint at any time to the relevant data protection authority in your country.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to fulfill your requests, provide you services, comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

If you receive emails from us about new or existing Lurn Products, Services and special offers specific to you, you can unsubscribe to our emails by clicking "unsubscribe" within each email. You may not opt-out of service-related communications, which are not promotional in nature.

### Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

As is true of most Sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, the files viewed on our site (e.g., HTML pages, graphics, etc.), operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data to analyze trends in the aggregate and administer the site.

Lurn uses cookies or similar technologies to store session information, analyze trends, administer the Sites, track users' movements around the Sites, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, which is sent to your browser from a website's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive.

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. We use session cookies to track your login status. This cookie is only ever transmitted over HTTPS. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. We use persistent cookies to determine from where you were referred to our Sites so that we may provide commissions or referral fees, and recognize the last user ID that you used to log in. We may set and access Lurn cookies on your computer; cookies are required to use the Sites.

You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's "help" directory. Please go to [www.aboutcookies.org](https://www.aboutcookies.org/) for more information on cookies, including how to disable them. If you choose to disable cookies, it may limit your use of certain features or functions on our Sites or service. To manage Flash cookies, please click here: <http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html>

### Third Party Tracking

Third parties also use cookies and other tracking technologies on our site, of which data is only collected in the aggregate. The use of cookies by third parties is not covered by our Privacy Policy. We do not have access or control over these cookies. Third parties use session ID and persistent cookies to make it easier for you to navigate the Sites, in order for you to use the shopping cart, and to otherwise use our services.

### Behavioral Targeting / Re-Targeting

We partner with a third party ad network to either display advertising on our Site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partner uses cookies and web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other websites. This information is used to provide you targeted advertising across the internet, based upon your interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by clicking [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/) (or if located in the European Union you may change your preferences by clicking [here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)). Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.

### Disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information

Our practices with respect to the disclosure of personally identifiable information include the following:

_Consent_. We may disclose your personally identifiable information to third parties with your express consent.

_Vendors and Affiliated Businesses_. We share your personally identifiable information with our parent company, affiliated businesses, and with the vendor(s) whose products you purchase, for their use in a manner described in this Privacy Policy.

_Agents/Service Providers_. We use third party service providers to assist us in providing our Services and Sites, including database backup providers to protect our data, and fraud prevention services. We may disclose your personally identifiable information to third parties who complete transactions or perform services on our behalf or for your benefit. We may utilize the services of third parties to verify customer data, or to supplement other information we have collected. We may also contract with third parties to host our Sites and to conduct market research. All service providers are authorized to use your personally identifiable information only as necessary to provide their respective services to us, and are obligated to protect your personally identifiable information under contract terms which are no less protective than those set forth in this Policy.

_Legal Process_. We may disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena or other legal process, or when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request.

_Certain Business Transfers_. Your personally identifiable information may be disclosed as part of a corporate business transaction, such as a merger, acquisition, joint venture, or financing or sale of Lurn assets, and could be transferred to a third party as one of the business assets in such a transaction. It may also be disclosed in the event of insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership. We will use reasonable efforts to direct any such transferee to use your personally identifiable information in a manner that is consistent with our Privacy Policy.

You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Sites of any change in ownership or uses of your personally identifiable information, as well as any resulting choices you may have regarding your personally identifiable information.

### Security

The security of your personally identifiable information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information such as credit card number on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using SSL.

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personally identifiable information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personally identifiable information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

The information we collect about you is stored in limited access servers. We maintain safeguards to protect the security of these servers and your personally identifiable information. We retain personally identifiable information only as long as necessary to complete a purchase, thwart fraud, or provide customer service.

### Links to Other Sites

If you click on a link to a third party site you will leave our site and go to the site you selected. Because we cannot control the activities of third parties, we cannot accept responsibility for any use of your personally identifiable information by such third parties, and we cannot guarantee that they will adhere to the same privacy practices as us. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any other site you visit or service provider from whom you request services.

### Changes to This Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, or by means of a notice on the Site. If we make any substantial change to the way we use your personally identifiable information, we will notify you by email. You will have an opportunity to opt out of such new or different uses of your personally identifiable information prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

### Lurn Contact Information

If you have any questions, comments or concerns about our Privacy Policy, you may contact us by submitting your inquiry to us at:

<https://lurn.com/contact>

To reach us by mail, please use the following address:

Lurn, Inc.  
2098 Gaither Road  
Rockville, MD 20850  
(888) 477 9719  
Support: Extension 6  
Lurn Center: Extension 2  

Please contact us if you have any further questions, or if you want to exercise any of your rights or to make a complaint. You also have the right to make a complaint to the supervisory authority in the country in which you are resident.

### International Transfers

Wherever you use our Site or access our Services, you understand and acknowledge that we may transfer, process, and store information about you in the United States and other countries, both within and outside of the European Economic Area. The countries to which we transfer your personal information may have different data protection laws than those in the country in which you reside.

OK We use cookies to offer you a better browsing experience, analyze site traffic, personalize content, and serve targeted advertisements. Read about how we use cookies on the [Privacy Policy](https://lurn.com/legal/privacy) page.
